https://www.farrier-reg.gov.uk/privacy

My FRC
About farriery
The Register of Farriers
What is a Farrier?
Professional & Personal Issues
Approved Training Farriers (ATFs)
The Register of Farriers
What is a Farrier?
Professional & Personal Issues
Approved Training Farriers (ATFs)
Privacy Policy
The Farriers Registration Council (FRC) aims to ensure that equines, through their owners, will be able to access the equine hoof-care that best meets their needs in a timely and assured manner: this care will be delivered only by those capable and qualified to do so.Whether you have a professional or public link to the FRC, we aim to be transparent about the data we hold about you. As the regulatory body for the farriery profession, we must retain and process personal data in order to fulfil our statutory functions acting in the public interest. Aside from these, we may retain and process personal information in order to implement various related policy and procedures.We are committed to protecting your personal and sensitive personal data; the purpose of our privacy policy is to give you a clear explanation about how we collect and process your personal data and further information can be obtained by downloading the Privacy policy.pdf below.Our website uses cookies, small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping baskets, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics; further information can be found by downloading the Cookies policy.pdf below.
Related Documents
FRC-0105 Cookies policy.pdf
0.17 MB
Privacy Policy - 03.04.19.pdf
0.25 MB
Data Protection and use of Farrier Data - 1 April 2018.pdf
0.23 MB
